Historical Photograph Collection: Glass-Plate Negatives Series, 1880-1920: Preliminary Finding Aid AC317
University Archives
- Buildings and Grounds, 1811-1944; 71 boxes
  - Witherspoon Hall, undated; 3 boxes
    - Witherspoon Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 183
    - Witherspoon, Undated; 1 box (Box 23)
      Plate number: 391
    - Witherspoon Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 533
- Carnegie Lake, 1917-1920; 5 boxes
  Glass plates within this series show views of Carnegie Lake.
  - Carnegie Lake, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
    Plate number: 197
  - Carnegie Lake, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 534-536, 538, 540, 542-548
  - Carnegie Lake with woods, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 537
  - Carnegie Lake with shore, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 539
  - Carnegie Lake through woods, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 541
  - Carnegie Lake Dam, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 549, 553
  - Carnegie Lake Dam in foreground, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 550-551
  - Carnegie Lake Dam, buildings on shore, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
  - Carnegie Lake, Harrioson Street bridge, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 554-556
  - Carnegie Lake with Washington Rd. bridge, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 557-560
  - Carnegie Lake with skaters, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 561-562
  - Carnegie Lake with people, bridge in background, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 563
  - Carnegie Lake, many canoes and people on shore, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 564
  - Carnegie Lake with Harrison Street bridge, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 565
  - Carnegie Lake with boats and canoes, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 566
  - Carnegie Lake with boat, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 567
  - Carnegie Lake with cow, Undated; 1 box (Box 28)
    Plate number: 568
  - Skating on Carnegie Lake, winter of 1917-18, 1917-1918; 1 box (Box 31)
    Original sleeve No. 106
    Plate number: 637
  - Carnegie Lake in winter of 1919, 1 box (Box 50)
    Original sleeve No. 447
    Plate number: 943
  - Carnegie Lake in winter of 1919-1920, 1 box (Box 50)
    Original sleeve No. 448
    Plate number: 944
  - Buildings and grounds, Carnegie Lake, Ice Hockey game, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
    Plate number: 1246
- Group Pictures, 1919; 2 boxes
  Glass plates within this series show groups of Princeton University students.
  - Undergraduate picture, fall of 1919, left section, 1 box (Box 33)
    Original sleeve No. 128
    Plate number: 659
  - Undergraduate picture, fall of 1919, middle section, 1 box (Box 33)
    Original sleeve No. 129
    Plate number: 660
  - Undergraduate picture, fall of 1919, right section, 1 box (Box 33)
    Original sleeve No. 130
    Plate number: 661
  - Class of 1919 on steps of Whig Hall, 1 box (Box 57)
    Original sleeve No. 1090
    Plate number: 1089
- Reunions, 1915-1919; 7 boxes
  Glass plates within this series show Princeton University reunions.
  - Reunion, class of 1847, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
    Plate number: 239
  - Reunion, class of 1876, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
    Plate number: 240
  - Reunion, class of 1882, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
    Plate number: 241-242
  - Reunions, grandstand university field, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
    Plate number: 243
  - Reunions, P-Rade, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
    Plate number: 244
  - Class of 1876 reunion, Undated; 1 box (Box 18)
    Plate number: 332-333
  - Class of 1885 reunion, Undated; 1 box (Box 18)
    Plate number: 334-336
  - Class of 1886 reunion, Undated; 1 box (Box 18)
    Plate number: 337
  - Class reunion?, Undated; 1 box (Box 20)
    Plate number: 348
  - Class reunion, Nassau Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 20)
    Plate number: 350
  - Class reunion, Undated; 2 boxes (Box 20, Box 21)
    Plate number: 351, 354-355
  - Class reunion, Graduate College, Undated; 2 boxes (Box 20, Box 21)
    Plate number: 352-353, 357-360
  - Class reunion, Nassau Hall lions, Undated; 1 box (Box 21)
    Plate number: 356
  - Reunions, Yale game P-Rade 1915, 1 box (Box 72)
    Plate number: 1378-1379
  - Reunions, Yale game P-Rade 1915, classics inside Osbourne Field Gate, 1 box (Box 72)
  - Reunions, Yale game P-Rade, oldest alumnus, Prospect St., 1915; 1 box (Box 72)
  - Reunions, Yale game P-Rade 1915, class of 1860 and crowd, 1 box (Box 72)
  - Reunions, Yale game P-Rade 1915, class of 1885, 1 box (Box 72)
  - Reunions, Yale game P-Rade 1915, class of 1895, 1 box (Box 73)
  - Reunions, Yale game P-Rade 1915, class of 1900, corner Nassau St. and University Place with horse and buggy and cars, 1915, 1 box (Box 73)
  - Reunions, Yale game P-Rade, 1915, class of 1900, 1 box (Box 73)
    Plate number: 1386-1388
  - Reunions, Yale game P-Rade, 1915, class of 1911, 1 box (Box 73)
  - Reunions, Yale game P-Rade, 1915, class of 1913, 1 box (Box 73)
  - Reunion banquet table, Undated; 1 box (Box 94)
    Emulsion layer damaged
  - 40 reunion group shot, straw hats, circa 1919, 1 box (Box 94)
- P-Rade and Other Parades, 1903-1922; 9 boxes
  Glass plates within this series show the Princeton P-Rade and other parades.
  - Senior parade 1904 with spectators in front of Whig or Clio, mocking Wilson's fence around Prospect built Sept. 1904, 1 box (Box 10)
    (See 1906 Bric-A-Brac p. 33)
    Plate number: 245
  - Senior parade 1905 with spectators in front of Clio, 1 box (Box 10)
    (See 1907 Bric-A-Brac p. 39)
    Plate number: 246
  - Senior parade 1903 in front of Whig or Clio, 1 box (Box 10)
    (See 1905 Bric-A-Brac p. 29) No paper print
    Plate number: 247
  - Senior parade 1904 with spectators in front of whig or clio, mocking Wilson's fence around Prospect built Sept. 1904, 1 box (Box 10)
    (See 1906 Bric-A-Brac p. 33) No paper print
    Plate number: 248
  - Senior parade or St. Patrick's Day parade, Fumigated Felixes, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
    Plate number: 249
  - Torchlight parade on Nassau Street, Undated; 1 box (Box 11)
    Plate number: 322
  - Senior parade? St. Patrick's Day parade? Fumigated Felixes, Undated; 1 box (Box 30)
    Plate number: 615-616
  - Freshman P-Rade leaving McCosh Hall for Flour picture, class of 1921, 1917; 1 box (Box 35)
    Original sleeve No. 170
    Plate number: 702
  - Freshman P-Rade passing chapel, class of 1921, 1917; 1 box (Box 35)
    Original sleeve No. 171
    Plate number: 703
  - Near view of freshman P-Rade, class of 1921., 1917; 1 box (Box 35)
    Original sleeve No. 172. Note Bill Rogers
    Plate number: 704
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, 1919, 1 box (Box 55)
    Original sleeve No. 1035
    Plate number: 1042
  - Freshman P-rade giving a locomotive flour picture, 1922, 1 box (Box 57)
    Original sleeve No. 1091
    Plate number: 1090
  - Junior high hat P-rade, class of 1921, 1 box (Box 57)
    Original sleeve No. 1094
    Plate number: 1093
  - Junior high hat P-rade, class of 1921, 1 box (Box 57)
    Original sleeve No. 1095
    Plate number: 1094
  - Juniors on Whig steps after high hat P-rade, class of 1921, 1 box (Box 57)
    Original sleeve No. 1096
    Plate number: 1095
  - St. Patrick's Day parade, Undated; 1 box (Box 66)
    Plate number: 1267-1272
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, Belgian relief float, Prospect St., 3/17/15, 1915; 1 box (Box 73)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, Belgian relief float, 1915, 1 box (Box 73)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, Bust Anybody's Cafe float, 1915, 1 box (Box 73)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, C.E. float. 1915, 1 box (Box 73)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, C.E. float. 1915, 1 box (Box 73)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, "Eugenics", 1915, 1 box (Box 73)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, 1915, ford ambulance, 1 box (Box 73)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, Huala Huala girls, 1915, 1 box (Box 73)
    Cracked
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, Jim Marshall in barrel, 1915, 1 box (Box 73)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, Jim Marshall with barrel, '79 HALL, 1915, 1 box (Box 74)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, Prospect Ave., Our Irish Dean with the Germans in Belgium, 1915, 1 box (Box 74)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parade, Saturday Night Club, Prospect St., 1915, 1 box (Box 74)
- 1920 Fire, 2 boxes
  Glass plates within this series capture the Friday May 14th, 1920 fire and its aftermath. The fire completly destroyed old Dickinson Hall and Marquand Chapel.
  - Dickinson Hall in flames, May, 1920, 1 box (Box 33)
    Original sleeve No. 143
    Plate number: 674
  - Tower falling in Dickinson Hall fire, 1920; 1 box (Box 34)
    Original sleeve No. 144
    Plate number: 675
  - Dickinson Hall fire, May, 1920, 1 box (Box 34)
    Original sleeve No. 145
    Plate number: 676
  - Chapel ruins from roof of McCosh Hall, May, 1920, 1 box (Box 34)
    Original sleeve No. 146
    Plate number: 677
  - Chapel ruins from rear, May, 1920, 1 box (Box 34)
    Original sleeve No. 147
    Plate number: 678
  - Chapel ruins from front, May, 1920, 1 box (Box 34)
    Original sleeve No. 148
    Plate number: 679
  - Side view of Chapel ruins, May, 1920, 1 box (Box 34)
    Original sleeve No. 149
    Plate number: 681
  - Dickinson Hall ruins, May, 1920, 1 box (Box 34)
    Original sleeve No. 150
    Plate number: 682
  - Front view of Dickinson Hall ruins, May, 1920, 1 box (Box 34)
    Original sleeve No. 151
    Plate number: 683
  - East end view of Dickenson Hall ruins, 1920; 1 box (Box 34)
    Original sleeve No. 152
    Plate number: 684
- Pyne Estate, 1919-1920; 3 boxes
  Glass plates within this series show the Pyne Estate, home of Moses Taylor Pyne.
  - Reg Lawrence at the Pyne Estate, October, 1919, 1 box (Box 40)
    Original sleeve No. 258
    Plate number: 775
  - Ralph Kent at the Pyne Estate, October, 1919, 1 box (Box 40)
    Original sleeve No. 259
    Plate number: 776
  - Reflections in pond at Pyne estate, October, 1919, 1 box (Box 40)
    Original sleeve No. 273
    Plate number: 777
  - Reflection of weeping willow tree at Pyne Estate, October, 1919, 1 box (Box 40)
    Original sleeve No. 274
    Plate number: 778
  - Shaded walk at the Pyne Estate, October, 1919, 1 box (Box 40)
    Original sleeve No. 275
    Plate number: 779
  - Weeping willow and bridge over pond in Pyne Estate, October, 1919, 1 box (Box 40)
    Original sleeve No. 276
    Plate number: 780
  - Path scene in Pyne Estate, Oct., 1919, 1 box (Box 40)
    Original sleeve No. 277. Remarks: Grade A1 picture
    Plate number: 781
  - Formal garden and house, Pyne Esate, March, 1919, 1 box (Box 40)
    Original sleeve No. 278
    Plate number: 782
  - The Pyne House seen through the pavillion March, 1920, 1 box (Box 40)
    Original sleeve No. 279
    Plate number: 783
  - Gold fish pool, Pyne Estate, March, 1920, 1 box (Box 40)
    Original sleeve No. 280
    Plate number: 784
  - Overarching beach tree, Pyne Estate, March, 1920, 1 box (Box 40)
    Original sleeve No. 281
    Plate number: 785
  - Pavillion and reflection, Pyne Estate, March, 1920, 1 box (Box 40)
    Original sleeve No. 282
    Plate number: 786
  - View along pond in Pyne Estate, May, 1920, 1 box (Box 40)
    Original sleeve No. 283
    Plate number: 787
  - Line of blooming pear trees at entrance to Pyne Estate, May, 1920, 1 box (Box 41)
    Original sleeve No. 284
    Plate number: 788
  - Pavillion and steps in Pyne Estate, May, 1920, 1 box (Box 41)
    Original sleeve No. 285
    Plate number: 789
  - Birch trees in the Pyne Estate, May, 1920, 1 box (Box 41)
    Original sleeve No. 286
    Plate number: 790
  - Arched path of Forsythias, Pyne Estate, 1920; 1 box (Box 41)
    Original sleeve No. 287
    Plate number: 791
  - Early spring view in Pyne Estate, 1920, 1 box (Box 41)
    Original sleeve No. 288
    Plate number: 792
  - Early spring view of pond in Pyne Estate, 1920, 1 box (Box 41)
    Original sleeve No. 289
    Plate number: 793
  - Jim Benson at the Pyne Estate, October, 1919, 1 box (Box 41)
    Original sleeve No. 300
    Plate number: 795
  - Mac Harper and Ray Sanger in pergola of Pyne Estate, Undated; 1 box (Box 57)
    Original sleeve No. 1073
    Plate number: 1079
  - Magnolia tree on Pyne Estate in bloom, 1919, 1 box (Box 57)
    Original sleeve No. 1084
    Plate number: 1086
- Artillery Exhibition, 1918-1919; 1 box
  Glass plates within this series show the 1919 Princeton Artillery Exhibition.
  - French 75 mm. in Princeton artillery exhibition, 1919, 1 box (Box 55)
    Original sleeve No. 1016
    Plate number: 1022
  - Field pieces in Princeton artillery unit exhibition, 1919, 1 box (Box 55)
    Original sleeve No. 1017
    Plate number: 1023
  - Field pieces in Princeton artillery unit exhibition, 1919, 1 box (Box 55)
    Original sleeve No. 1018
    Plate number: 1024
  - Large gun in Princeton field artillery exhibit, 1919, 1 box (Box 55)
    Original sleeve No. 1019
    Plate number: 1025
  - Erecting artillery observation tower at artillery exhibit, 1919, 1 box (Box 55)
    Original sleeve No. 1020
    Plate number: 1026
  - Captured german guns on exhibition at Princeton, 1919, 1 box (Box 55)
    Original sleeve No. 1021
    Plate number: 1027
  - Captured german guns on exhibition at Princeton, 1918, 1 box (Box 55)
    Original sleeve No. 1022
    Plate number: 1028
- Commencement, 1918-1919; 2 boxes
  Glass plates within this series show Princeton University Commencement Day.
  - Faculty procession on commencement day, 1918, 1 box (Box 55)
    Original sleeve No. 1029
    Plate number: 1035
  - Memorial service at commencement exercises, 1919, 1 box (Box 57)
    Original sleeve No. 1089
    Plate number: 1088
- R.O.T.C. and S.A.T.C., 1917-1919; 4 boxes
  Glass plates within this series concern Princeton R.O.T.C. and S.A.T.C. activities.
  - Captain Cornelius, Canadian Army, R.O.T.C., spring of 1918, 1 box (Box 31)
    Original sleeve No. 97
    Plate number: 628
  - Princeton R.O.T.C. being reviewed by French officers in 1918, 1 box (Box 55)
    Original sleeve No. 1032
    Plate number: 1039
  - American and French officers reviewing Princeton, R.O.T.C, 1919, 1 box (Box 55)
    Original sleeve No. 1033
    Plate number: 1040
  - Captain Desformestreaux and others in alumni day procession, 1918, 1 box (Box 55)
    Original sleeve No. 1034
    Plate number: 1041
  - Digging trenches near stadium, 1918, R.O.T.C., 1 box (Box 57)
    Original sleeve No. 1088
    Plate number: 1087
  - Princeton R.O.T.C. in hollow square formation being addressed by Col. Pearson, 1918, 1 box (Box 57)
    Original sleeve No. 1092
    Plate number: 1091
  - Range finding devices of artillery unit, 1918, 1 box (Box 57)
    Original sleeve No. 1093
    Plate number: 1092
  - Lieutenant Charles Ringwalt, 1919, 1 box (Box 57)
    Original sleeve No. 1074
    Plate number: 1080
  - R.O.T.C. companies forming in front of Little Hall, 1917, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1103
    Plate number: 1101
  - Present arms, Princeton R.O.T.C., 1917, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1104
    Plate number: 1102
  - The awkward squad, spring of 1917, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1105
    Plate number: 1103
  - Stack arms, Princeton R.O.T.C., 1917, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1106
    Plate number: 1104
  - Column of squads Princeton R.O.T.C., 1917, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1107
    Plate number: 1105
  - Fall in at attention Princeotn R.O.T.C., 1917, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1108
    Plate number: 1106
  - Colonel Pearson, Undated; 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1109
    Plate number: 1107
  - Raising flag of aviation school, 1917, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1110
    Plate number: 1108
  - Trench digging, 1917, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1111
    Plate number: 1109
  - Flag raising ceremony, Princeton aviation school, 1918, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1112
    Plate number: 1110
  - Trenches near the stadium spring of 1918, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1113
    Plate number: 1111
  - Trench digging, 1918, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1114
    Plate number: 1112
  - Red Cross Parade, in Liberty Loan campaign, 1917, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1115
    Plate number: 1113
  - Topography, R.O.T.C., 1917, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1116
    Plate number: 1114
  - Trenches near stadium, 1918, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1117
    Plate number: 1115
  - Harold Wanless and Jim Armstrong in 10 E.M.W., winter of 1917, 1 box (Box 31)
    Original sleeve No. 87
    Plate number: 619
  - Portrait of Reg. Lawrence, 61 Holder, S.A.T.C., November, 1918, 1 box (Box 31)
    Original sleeve No. 88-89
    Plate number: 620-621
  - Portrait of Ralph Kent, 61 Holder, S.A.T.C., November, 1918, 1 box (Box 31)
    Original sleeve No. 90
    Plate number: 622
  - Portrait of Harold Wanless, November, 1918, S.A.T.C., 61 Holder Hall, 1 box (Box 31)
    Original sleeve No. 91
    Plate number: 623
  - Ralph Kent, Reg Lawrence, Ray Sanger, and Harold Wanless, November, 1918, S.A.T.C, 1 box (Box 31)
    Original sleeve No. 92
    Plate number: 624
  - Col. Pearson commander of S.A.T.C., 1918, 1 box (Box 58)
    Original sleeve No. 1101
    Plate number: 1100
- Student Activities, 1890-1922; 17 boxes
  Glass plates within this series concern the activites of Princeton University students.
  - Class day 1890, 1890-1892; 2 boxes (Box 17, Box 18)
    Plate number: 325-331
  - Student group, Nassau Lit?, Undated; 1 box (Box 19)
    Plate number: 341
  - Misobservance of freshman customs by Class of 1921, winter of 1917, 1 box (Box 31)
    Original sleeve No. 98
    Plate number: 629
  - Princeton students returning from Christmas vacation, January, 1918, 1 box (Box 31)
    Original sleeve No. 105
    Plate number: 636
  - Cane Spree in front of Witherspoon Hall, November, 1919, 1 box (Box 32)
    Original sleeve No. 108
    Plate number: 639
  - Senior singing, spring of 1919, 1 box (Box 32)
    Original sleeve No. 120
    Plate number: 651
  - Flour Picture, 1917-1922; 3 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show images related to the freshman hazing ritual know as the "flour picture".
    - Freshman taking steps of Whig Hall, class of 1921, 1917; 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 173
      Plate number: 705
    - Water from above for the freshman flour picture, class of 1921, 1917; 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 174
      Plate number: 706
    - Freshman flour picture, class of 1921, 1917; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 175
      Plate number: 707
    - Sophmores on roof of Whig Hall at 1922 flour picture, 1 box (Box 55)
      Original sleeve No. 1023
      Plate number: 1029
    - 1922 flour picture, 1 box (Box 55)
      Original sleeve No. 1024
      Plate number: 1030
    - 1922 besieged by flour, backed to the wall, 1919, 1 box (Box 55)
      Original sleeve No. 1025
      Plate number: 1031
    - 1922 taking the steps in flour picture, 1919, 1 box (Box 55)
      Original sleeve No. 1026
      Plate number: 1032
    - 1922 rushing for the steps for flour picture, 1919, 1 box (Box 55)
      Original sleeve No. 1027
      Plate number: 1033
  - Theatre, 1919-1920; 5 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries capture images of Princeton University Theatre performances.
    - Stage set of Theatre Intime in 20 E.W., Undated; 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 165
      Plate number: 697
    - Reg Lawrence as Lady Macbeth in Theatre Intime in 20 E. Witherspoon, Undated; 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 166
      Plate number: 698
    - Ralph Kent and Lindabury in "Fame and the Poet", Theatre Intime, 1920, 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 167
      Plate number: 699
    - Reg Lawrence and Chanler Hale as "Dalila and Sampson", 1920, 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 168
      Plate number: 700
    - Chanler Hale and Reg Lawrence as "Sampson and Delila", 1920; 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 169
      Plate number: 701
    - Charles Scribner in the Isle of Surprise, 1919, 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 176
      Plate number: 708
    - Irving Harris as the villain in the Isle of Surprise, 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 177
      Plate number: 709
    - End of the first act of the Isle of Surprise, 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 178
      Plate number: 710
    - Walter Folmer and Russ Forgan in the Isle of Surprise "Namonia and Johnny Topley", 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 179
      Plate number: 711
    - "Isle of Surprise", 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 180. Front row, Maury Trimble and Jack Strubing
      Plate number: 712
    - Russ Forgan and Walter Folmer in the Isle of Surprise, 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 181
      Plate number: 713
    - The three potentates, Gilbert, Kaufmann, and Osborne, in the Isle of Surprise, 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 182
      Plate number: 714
    - Reg Lawrence as Claribel in the Isle of Surprise, 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 183
      Plate number: 715
    - Elijah Boteler in the Isle of Surprise, 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 184
      Plate number: 716
    - Brennan, 1922, as the princess in the Isle of Surprise, 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 185
      Plate number: 717
    - Frank Chapman and Reg Lawrence in the Isle of Surprise, 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 186
      Plate number: 718
    - Percy Cowan and Charles Schribner in the Isle of Surprise, 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 187
      Plate number: 719
    - First act costume of Walter Folmer in the Isle of Surprise, 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 188
      Plate number: 720
    - Second act costume of Walter Folmer in Isle of Surprise, 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Original sleeve No. 189
      Plate number: 721
    - First act costume of Walter Folmer in the Isle of Surprise, 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Plate is missing. Original sleeve No. 190. Color plate
      Plate number: 722
    - Second act costume of Walter Folmer in Isle of Surprise, 1919; 1 box (Box 36)
      Plate is missing. Original sleeve No. 191. Color plate
      Plate number: 723
    - Men and women on stage, play?, Undated; 1 box (Box 90)
  - Princeton University group on steps, 1906?, circa 1906; 1 box (Box 63)
    Plate number: 1220
  - Friars Club, 1908, 1 box (Box 63)
    Plate number: 1221
  - Friars Club, 1909, 1908; 1 box (Box 63)
    Plate number: 1222
  - Alumni Day, '03 representatives in front of Palmer Lab, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
    Plate number: 1223
  - Student activities "Big Ring" around cannon, Undated; 1 box (Box 66)
    Plate number: 1273-1274
  - Student activities, Camera Club exhibition, Nassau Hall room 10, Undated; 1 box (Box 66)
  - Student activities, Camera Club exhibition, Nassau Hall room 11, Undated; 1 box (Box 66)
  - Student activities, chess, Undated; 1 box (Box 66)
  - Student activities, class of 1918 showing new rain and show hats, Dec. 1914, 1 box (Box 66)
  - Student activities, class of 1918 in new rain and show hats, photo taken from above, Dec. 1914, 1 box (Box 66)
  - Student activities, class of 1918 in new rain and show hats, Dec. 1914, 1 box (Box 66)
  - Student activities, debaters at work, 1915?, circa 1915; 1 box (Box 66)
    Plate number: 1281-1282
  - Student activities, Eating Clubs bicker, Nassau Street, Undated; 1 box (Box 66)
  - Student activities, gym rush, 1918 vs. 1919, Undated; 1 box (Box 66)
  - Student activities, gym rush, 1918 vs. 1919, Proctor Bill Coan in action, Undated; 1 box (Box 67)
  - Student activities, gym rush, 1918 vs. 1919, Undated; 1 box (Box 67)
  - Student activities, gym rush, 1918 vs. 1919, Undated; 1 box (Box 67)
    Showing return of 1919 from gym because of death of one of their members (Ephraim Stockton Wells)
  - Student activities, Junior High hat parade, Undated; 1 box (Box 67)
    Plate number: 1288-1292